<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Iain</title>
    <link>http://yanlistat.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Iain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 &amp;#183; Yan Li</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://yanlistat.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yanlistat.com/home/hero_carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yanlistat.com/home/hero_carousel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yanlistat.com/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yanlistat.com/home/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;biography&#34;&gt;Biography&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p class=&#34;text-justify&#34;&gt;I&#39;m pursuing my Ph.D. degree in Statistics at &lt;a
href=&#34;http://stat.uconn.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; ref=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;
Departmemt of Statistics, University of Connecticut&lt;/a&gt; after
graduating from &lt;a href=&#34;http://stat.ruc.edu.cn&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;
ref=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;School of Statistics&lt;/a&gt;, Renmin University of China in
2016. My interests lie in developing and applying statistical models
to different fields of research. I am also interested in how
statistics can help with interpreting data and make contribution to
researches in different area. I&#39;m currently working on
error-in-variables model and detection &amp; attribution of climate
change. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p class=&#34;text-justify&#34;&gt;I started this website to post some thinkings
and personal notes on statistical project and programming. I would be
glad if my humble opinions turn out to be helpful in your researches
or studies. &lt;/p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Posts</title>
      <link>http://yanlistat.com/home/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yanlistat.com/home/posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://yanlistat.com/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yanlistat.com/home/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://yanlistat.com/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yanlistat.com/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Several Things for Writing Statistical Paper</title>
      <link>http://yanlistat.com/post/2018-09-11-writing_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yanlistat.com/post/2018-09-11-writing_paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;1. Keep tex source file clean and tidy. Make everything easy to read and
compare. No extra spacing or indention, and two blank lines for
separating paragraph. Make line width under 80. While do not limit
math expression to 80. Break math expression at right places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. Make notations, equations precise and concise, and explain clearly
meaning of each notation. Do not use abbreviation if unnecessary. The
notations should be consistent through the paper. Leave enough spaces
so the formulas become more readable even in source and only number
equation if it’s referenced. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3. When citing a paper, do not cite the reviewing paper, cite the
original paper. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4. The caption of table and figure should be self contained. Make
sure others can under- stand the figures or tables by reading the
caption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5. Tables should be formatted in logical order to make the tables
easy to follow. Content in one column should be consistent. Do not
change the font size in table. Reformat the table to fit the page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6. In introduction section, when doing literature review, one
should make connection to the paper. Do not just describe the previous
work. And the introduction should be in logical order to make it easy
to follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7. Always explain the unusual findings in the numerical studies
section, and also consider addressing other questions that the readers
may ask.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>